Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65
- The Garment Worker, 1958-1962 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 45: The Garment Worker, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.47 (1962: July 6)
  - Item 46: The Garment Worker, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.48 (1962: Aug. 3)
  - Item 47: The Garment Worker, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.49 (1962: Sept. 7)
  - Item 48: The Garment Worker, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.50 (1962: Oct. 5)
  - Item 49: The Garment Worker, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.51 (1962: Nov. 2)
  - Item 50: The Garment Worker, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.52 (1962: Dec. 7)
- The Garment Worker, 1963-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.1 (1963: Jan. 4)
  - Item 2: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.2 (1963: Feb. 1)
  - Item 3: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.3 (1963: Mar. 1)
  - Item 4: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.4 (1963: Apr. 5)
  - Item 5: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.5 (1963: May 3)
  - Item 6: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.6 (1963: June 7)
  - Item 7: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.7 (1963: July 5)
  - Item 8: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.8 (1963: Aug. 2)
  - Item 9: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.9 (1963: Sept. 6)
  - Item 10: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.10 (1963: Oct. 4)
  - Item 11: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.11 (1963: Nov. 1)
  - Item 12: The Garment Worker, 1963; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.12 (1963: Dec. 6)
  - Item 13: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.13 (1964: Jan. 3)
  - Item 14: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.14 (1964: Feb. 7)
  - Item 15: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.15 (1964: Mar. 6)
  - Item 16: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.16 (1964: Apr. 3)
  - Item 17: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.17 (1964: May 1)
  - Item 18: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.18 (1964: June 5)
  - Item 19: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.19 (1964: July 3)
  - Item 20: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.20 (1964: Aug. 7)
  - Item 21: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.21 (1964: Sept. 4)
  - Item 22: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.22 (1964: Oct. 2)
  - Item 23: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.23 (1964: Nov. 6)
  - Item 24: The Garment Worker, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.24 (1964: Dec. 4)
  - Item 25: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.25 (1965: Jan. 8)
  - Item 26: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.26 (1965: Feb. 5)
  - Item 27: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.27 (1965: Mar. 5)
  - Item 28: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.28 (1965: Apr. 2)
  - Item 29: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.29 (1965: May 7)
  - Item 30: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.30 (1965: June 4)
  - Item 31: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.31 (1965: July 2)
  - Item 32: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.32 (1965: Aug. 6)
  - Item 33: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.33 (1965: Sept. 3)
  - Item 34: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.34 (1965: Oct. 1)
  - Item 35: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.35 (1965: Nov. 5)
  - Item 36: The Garment Worker, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.36 (1965: Dec. 3)
  - Item 37: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.37 (1966: Jan. 7)
  - Item 38: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.38 (1966: Feb. 4)
  - Item 39: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.39 (1966: Mar. 4)
  - Item 40: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.40 (1966: Apr. 1)
  - Item 41: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.41 (1966: May 6)
  - Item 42: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.42 (1966: June 3)
  - Item 43: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.43 (1966: July 1)
  - Item 44: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.44 (1966: Aug. 5)
  - Item 45: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.45 (1966: Sept. 2)
  - Item 46: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.46 (1966: Oct. 7)
  - Item 47: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.47 (1966: Nov. 4)
  - Item 48: The Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.48 (1966: Dec. 2)
  - Item 49: The Garment Worker, 1967; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.49 (1967: Jan. 6)
  - Item 50: The Garment Worker, 1967; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.50 (1967: Feb. 3)
  - Item 51: The Garment Worker, 1967; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.51 (1967: Mar. 3)
  - Item 52: The Garment Worker, 1967; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.52 (1967: Apr. 7)
  - Item 53: The Garment Worker, 1967; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.53 (1967: May 5)
- Hat Work, 1939; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Hat Work, 1939; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Author: United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Works International Union
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1939: June)
  - Item 2: Hat Work, 1939; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.7 (1939: July)
  - Item 3: Hat Work, 1939; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.8 (1939: Aug.)
  - Item 4: Hat Work, 1939; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.9 (1939: Sept.)
  - Item 5: Hat Work, 1939; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.10 (1939: Oct.)
  - Item 6: Hat Work, 1939; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.11 (1939: Nov.)
  - Item 7: Hat Work, 1939; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.12 (1939: Dec.)
- Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1940: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1940: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1940: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1940: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1940: May)
  - Item 6: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.6 (1940: June)
  - Item 7: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.7 (1940: July)
  - Item 8: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.8 (1940: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.9 (1940: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.10 (1940: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.11 (1940: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Hat Work, 1940; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.12 (1940: Dec.)
- Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1941: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1941: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1941: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1941: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1941: May)
  - Item 6: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1941: June)
  - Item 7: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.7 (1941: July)
  - Item 8: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.8 (1941: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.9 (1941: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.10 (1941: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.11 (1941: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Hat Work, 1941; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.12 (1941: Dec.)
- Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1942: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1942: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1942: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1942: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1942: May)
  - Item 6: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.6 (1942: June)
  - Item 7: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (1942: July)
  - Item 8: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.5:no.8 (1942: Aug.)
- Hat Work, 1942-1944 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.5:no.9 (1942: Sept.)
  - Item 2: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.5:no.10 (1942: Oct.)
  - Item 3: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (1942: Nov.)
  - Item 4: Hat Work, 1942; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.5:no.12 (1942: Dec.)
  - Item 5: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1943: Jan.)
  - Item 6: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1943: Feb.)
  - Item 7: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1943: Mar.)
  - Item 8: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1943: Apr.)
  - Item 9: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1943: May)
  - Item 10: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1943: June)
  - Item 11: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1943: July)
  - Item 12: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.8 (1943: Aug.)
  - Item 13: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (1943: Sept.)
  - Item 14: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.10 (1943: Oct.)
  - Item 15: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.11 (1943: Nov.)
  - Item 16: Hat Work, 1943; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.6:no.12 (1943: Dec.)
  - Item 17: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1944: Jan.)
  - Item 18: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1944: Feb.)
  - Item 19: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1944: Mar.)
  - Item 20: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1944: Apr.)
  - Item 21: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1944: May)
  - Item 22: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (1944: June)
  - Item 23: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.7 (1944: July)
  - Item 24: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.8 (1944: Aug.)
  - Item 25: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.9 (1944: Sept.)
  - Item 26: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1944: Oct.)
  - Item 27: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.11 (1944: Nov.)
  - Item 28: Hat Work, 1944; Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.12 (1944: Dec.)
- Industry, 1924-1925 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Author: Associated Industries f Massachusetts
    Notes: v.14:no.1 (1924: Sept. 6)
  - Item 2: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.2 (1924: Sept. 13)
  - Item 3: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.3 (1924: Sept. 20)
  - Item 4: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.4 (1924: Sept. 27)
  - Item 5: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.5 (1924: Oct. 4)
  - Item 6: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.6 (1924: Oct. 11)
  - Item 7: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.7 (1924: Oct. 18)
  - Item 8: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.8 (1924: Oct. 25)
  - Item 9: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.9 (1924: Nov. 1)
  - Item 10: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.10 (1924: Nov. 8)
  - Item 11: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.11 (1924: Nov. 15)
  - Item 12: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.12 (1924: Nov. 22)
  - Item 13: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.13 (1924: Nov. 29)
  - Item 14: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.14 (1924: Dec. 6)
  - Item 15: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.15 (1924: Dec. 13)
  - Item 16: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.16 (1924: Dec. 20)
  - Item 17: Industry, 1924; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.17 (1924: Dec. 27)
  - Item 18: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.18 (1925: Jan. 3)
  - Item 19: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.19 (1925: Jan. 10)
  - Item 20: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.20 (1925: Jan. 17)
  - Item 21: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.21 (1925: Jan. 24)
  - Item 22: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.22 (1925: Jan. 31)
  - Item 23: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.23 (1925: Feb. 7)
  - Item 24: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.24 (1925: Feb. 14)
  - Item 25: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.25 (1925: Feb. 21)
  - Item 26: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.26 (1925: Feb. 28)
- Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.1 (1925: Mar. 7)
  - Item 2: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.2 (1925: Mar. 14)
  - Item 3: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.3 (1925: Mar. 21)
  - Item 4: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.4 (1925: Mar. 28)
  - Item 5: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.5 (1925: Apr. 4)
  - Item 6: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.6 (1925: Apr. 11)
  - Item 7: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.7 (1925: Apr. 18)
  - Item 8: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.8 (1925: Apr. 25)
  - Item 9: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.9 (1925: May 2)
  - Item 10: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.10 (1925: May 9)
  - Item 11: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.11 (1925: May 16)
  - Item 12: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.12 (1925: May 23)
  - Item 13: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.13 (1925: May 30)
  - Item 14: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.14 (1925: June 6)
  - Item 15: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.15 (1925: June 13)
  - Item 16: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.16 (1925: June 20)
  - Item 17: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.17 (1925: June 27)
  - Item 18: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.18 (1925: July 4)
  - Item 19: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.19 (1925: July 11)
  - Item 20: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.20 (1925: July 18)
  - Item 21: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.21 (1925: July 25)
  - Item 22: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.22 (1925: Aug. 1)
  - Item 23: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.23 (1925: Aug. 8)
  - Item 24: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.24 (1925: Aug. 15)
  - Item 25: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.25 (1925: Aug. 22)
  - Item 26: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.26 (1925: Aug. 29)
- Industry, 1925-1926 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.1 (1925: Sept. 5)
  - Item 2: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.2 (1925: Sept. 12)
  - Item 3: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.3 (1925: Sept. 19)
  - Item 4: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.4 (1925: Sept. 26)
  - Item 5: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.5 (1925: Oct. 3)
  - Item 6: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.6 (1925: Oct. 10)
  - Item 7: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.7 (1925: Oct. 17)
  - Item 8: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.8 (1925: Oct. 24)
  - Item 9: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.9 (1925: Oct. 31)
  - Item 10: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.10 (1925: Nov. 7)
  - Item 11: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.11 (1925: Nov. 14)
  - Item 12: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.12 (1925: Nov. 21)
  - Item 13: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.13 (1925: Nov. 28)
  - Item 14: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.14 (1925: Dec. 5)
  - Item 15: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.15 (1925: Dec. 12)
  - Item 16: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.16 (1925: Dec. 19)
  - Item 17: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.17 (1925: Dec. 26)
  - Item 18: Industry, 1925; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.18 (1926: Jan. 2)
  - Item 19: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.19 (1926: Jan. 9)
  - Item 20: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.20 (1926: Jan. 16)
  - Item 21: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.21 (1926: Jan. 23)
  - Item 22: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.22 (1926: Jan. 31)
  - Item 23: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.23 (1926: Feb. 6)
  - Item 24: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.24 (1926: Feb. 13)
  - Item 25: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.25 (1926: Feb. 20)
  - Item 26: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.26 (1926: Feb. 27)
- Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1926: Mar. 6)
  - Item 2: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.2 (1926: Mar. 13)
  - Item 3: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.3 (1926: Mar. 20)
  - Item 4: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.4 (1926: Mar. 27)
  - Item 5: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.5 (1926: Apr. 3)
  - Item 6: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.6 (1926: Apr. 10)
  - Item 7: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.7 (1926: Apr. 17)
  - Item 8: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.8 (1926: Apr. 24)
  - Item 9: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.9 (1926: May 1)
  - Item 10: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.10 (1926: May 8)
  - Item 11: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.11 (1926: May 15)
  - Item 12: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.12 (1926: May 22)
  - Item 13: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.13 (1926: May 29)
  - Item 14: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.14 (1926: June 5)
  - Item 15: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.15 (1926: June 12)
  - Item 16: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.16 (1926: June 19)
  - Item 17: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.17 (1926: June 26)
  - Item 18: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.18 (1926: July 3)
  - Item 19: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.19 (1926: July 10)
  - Item 20: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.20 (1926: July 17)
  - Item 21: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.21 (1926: July 24)
  - Item 22: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.22 (1926: July 31)
  - Item 23: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.23 (1926: Aug. 7)
  - Item 24: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.24 (1926: Aug. 14)
  - Item 25: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.25 (1926: Aug. 21)
  - Item 26: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.17:no.26 (1926: Aug. 28)
- Industry, 1926-1927 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.1 (1926: Sept. 4)
  - Item 2: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.2 (1926: Sept. 11)
  - Item 3: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.3 (1926: Sept. 18)
  - Item 4: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.4 (1926: Sept. 25)
  - Item 5: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.5 (1926: Oct. 2)
  - Item 6: Industry, 1926; Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.18:no.6 (1926: Oct. 9)